Heat. Heat.
All right, y'all. We are live on this
beautiful Monday afternoon. God bless
everybody in Jesus name. In Yeshua's
name. I do pray you and your family are
all super blessed. Guys, Bitcoin, what
what what the actual, man. Like,
honestly, what is going on? We're
rejecting from a value area high. We're
bouncing from a PC. We're holding the
trend line, but we're breaking market
structure. I mean, are we bullish? Are
we bearish? What is going on? I mean,
the trades are still open, guys. I'm
still long. I'm still short.
All right, we're going to be discussing
what's going on today, guys. Make sure
to smash up the like. All right, make
sure to smash up the like. And here's
the thing, guys. I do have to make a
very special announcement today.
The special announcement is this, guys.
Um, you know, Blowfin now every week is
going to be giving away $2,000.
$2,000 every single week.
Can you believe it? Let's Let's dis
Let's talk about it real quick. All
right. Every single week, Blow Fin is
giving away two grand.
All you got to do is post your P&Ls in
the Discord. You don't have to be a VIP.
This is available to everybody. All
right. Every single person right now has
the ability
to partake in this $2,000 giveaway every
single week. All right. What you have to
do is you have to post a screenshot of
your Jason Casper custom P&L cards in
the blowfin PNL channel. All right. Now,
who you know, like I said before, this
picture makes me very uncomfortable. And
to think that you guys are going to be
looking at this every trade you take
makes me even more uncomfortable. But
you know what? Look, it's about money,
man. What's more important? Money or
feeling uncomfortable? You know what I
mean? So, if you're interested in that,
head on over to the free Discord. Go
check it out. Read the rules and all
that stuff. It's It's going to be a good
time. Who doesn't like a little bit of
free money here and there? You know what
I'm saying? Who doesn't like a little
bit of free money? I'll tell you, I love
some free money myself.
Now, let's uh big give a big shout out
to everybody in the chit chat here. Big
shout out to Benny Blanco from the
Bronx. He says, "God bless." Shout out
to Don Give for Dam who says, "Br."
Shout out to Maju 3384 who says, "Money,
peace." Shout out to Venvoki. Shout out
to Skywalker. Shout out to Kodak 4737.
Follow the cycle. Nothing new under the
sun. That's true. There's nothing new
under the sun. Sometimes people might
say, "Hey, this is new." But really,
it's been done before, right? There's
nothing new under the sun. What the
actual Shout out to Prime Vids. Shout
out to Senor. He says, "Jason Casper
doesn't use soap. I usually don't use
soap." And that's the truth about Jason
Casper. He usually doesn't use soap. All
right. I'm getting a little bit dirty. I
was looking at my skin today thinking,
man, man,
it's looking kind of gross, you know.
[music] It's looking kind of gross.
Shout out to Joanie HSV. Yo, greetings
from Germany. Shout out to Bullish on
Parade. He says the song's going to make
Link go to the moon. Pun intended. Shout
out to Jose. Shout out to Dimarret who
says Mo.
Big shout out to Felu 8888
who says, "I'm back. Starting to
accumulate. Just grab some Etherum."
Major shout out to Preparing for War.
Major shout out to Splash Films. Major
shout to Bloxburg. Yeah, we got the
Zelda theme for some reason was in my
head. So, I figured, hey,
when the Zelda theme is in your head,
sometimes you just got to start the
stream with it. You know what I mean? I
don't know why it was in my head. I was
feeding the chickens just singing
So, I just figured I'd go with it, man.
I don't know why. Big shout out to
everyone in here. Dispensational
pre-millennialism.
Shout out to my man Cryptocowpoke.
Um, and Jay Becker and Manuel 12255
[music] and Lady Pipskiller. I hope I
will be one of them. You might be one of
the lucky winners that wins the $2,000
prize.
All right. So, so, so, so go go go sign
up to Blofen. You know, Blofin,
to be honest with you, Blofin. What's
this? Here we go. Blowin. All right. Not
only are they giving away $2,000 a week,
but they also have this juicy whales
setup campaign here. All right. Let's
not forget good old Bitbase is also
giving away $500 a week.
And good old Bitbas is giving you all
this juicy goodness plus VIP level seven
fees. Man, the exchanges here I do have
to say this. All right, the the
exchanges are are going all out, guys,
during the bare market to make sure that
us traders are satisfied with all the
juicy goodness.
All right, with all the juicy goodness.
Bitcoin rejecting from resistance here,
unable to break out, unable to break the
$67,000 level. It's going to be a big
week, guys. this week, as many of us
know, on Wednesday, FOMC,
the good old interest rate decision.
[music] And look, I'm not really
expecting anything big from it, but
typically that that does result in some
volatility. And the volatility indeed
oftent times does give us a
an entry or a move. All right, it's the
beginning of a move, you know.
Um,
how do you know if you're signed up
under your link? I'm not actually sure
how you know. I'm not sure. All right.
Shout out to Rev. David. He says, "All
be blessed." Well, may you be blessed,
too. Dr. Pancake says, "God is good."
Amen, bro. God is so good. Amen. God is
so good. Shout out to Save the
Republic's USA. Shout out to
Constitutional Republic. Stop with the
World Cup shenanigans and let's save the
republic here in the USA. Cool. I just
read your whole little thing there. Not
even sure what it means, bro. I don't
really know what it means. I'm just a
purple hatw wearing treadmill walking
kind of guy. You know what I'm saying?
Uh can't wait to get lied to about
inflation. El inflation
seen.
Yeah, but who really cares about
inflation? Honestly, like that's the
thing. Like I don't care about it. I
don't know. Maybe you guys care about
it. personally don't really care about
inflation. The reason why I don't care
about inflation is because it's not
going to get any better. It's only going
to get worse until the currency either
hyperinflates or the whole system
collapses. That's just it is what it is,
[music] right? So, because that's
inevitable, we shouldn't be worried
about inflation. Instead, we should be
worried about, man, because it's
inevitable, because there's either going
to be a currency collapse or a currency
hyperinflationary event. What can we do
in the meantime in order to be prepared
for war? You know, preparing for war.
You know what I'm talking about, man?
Like, what can we do to be prepared? I
don't know. We could like learn how to
trade. We could start businesses. We
could start homesteads. we can start
growing our own food, raising our own
animals, trying to get off grid, trying
to establish strong communities locally
of like-minded people, you know, just to
be prepared, [music] you know, instead
of worrying about inflation. But I I I
like it when they come out and lie to
me. I like when Kevin W. I like when he
lies to me. I like I you know, Kevin,
just just lie to me, man. There's
something inside when Kevin Walsh lies
to me.
It makes me feel
something.
Now, let's see.
Let's pop back into the Bitcoin price,
guys. As you can see here on this chart,
it is a brand new week. And with the
brand new week comes a brand new weekly
candle. And I have two volume profiles
pulled up here on the chart. Let's start
with the first volume profile. First of
all, I do want to say this, guys. Last
week's
volume profile has taken a turn for the
unexpected. All right. What do I mean by
that? Well, let's go ahead and take a
look at a little history. If we unextend
this thing [music] to the right, to the
left, should I say? Unextend it to the
left. Let's let's pull it here. No,
let's pull it here. Let's pull it here.
Okay, unextend it to the left. You can
see that the high volume node used to be
at the exact price. And this is on Bybit
USD, the only chart that matters, by the
way, in my mind. All right, I know other
traders use Coinbase and all this.
[music]
The high volume node used to be at
$66,832.88.
[music] We rejected perfectly to the
dollar from it last week. All right.
Now, fast forward to this week and
what's happened. The majority of the
volume now has shifted. Yes, we still
have a high volume node up here at
66832, but right now the highest volume
of the range is down here at 63957
and 90. Why is that significant? It is
significant because what we have here is
a confirmed bullish divergence on the
weekly as the price is getting lower
into key support. Remember this is a
macro Fibonacci golden pocket. Why we
took the long in the Casper Crew VIP
Discord on June 25th at 10:02 a.m. We
are seeing the momentum waves getting
higher over time. a big juicy wave
followed by a skinny wave bullish
divergence. And now we've confirmed a
blue weekly candle
above the PC. And not only that, when we
look at it in hindsight, it looks pretty
nice because it's a blue doge,
a blue Dogecoin candle. We got the wick
coming down and this wick is pretty much
bouncing off the previous weekly open
and then boom, straight up. So, it looks
kind of nice. And if we go to the daily
time frame, we can see that
interestingly enough after the
rejection, we did bounce off the
previous weekly open here and we're
holding support on this PC.
So, so far we're holding support on the
PC and now we're seeing a Z money flow
on the daily cross and a potential green
dot about to print.
Now, in the context of having printed a
nice bullish divergence at the low at
key support, flipping the now PC from
resistance into support and about to get
a green dot on the daily after a fresh
money flow cross, it just makes me feel
all right. Now, you can't trade on your
feelings, but it really does make me
feel like these highs are inevitably
inevitably inevitably inevitably
going to be taken out, right? inevitably
going to be taken out. You know what I
mean?
Like um
yeah, I just feel like we're probably
going to go for this level. Now, I could
be totally wrong. We very well may um
lose the PC and and if we do, guys, then
I have I will have to change my tune.
Here's why I have to change my tune.
Because right now, this is [music] the
very critical support here. If we lose
it now, we're making a lower low. All
right, we're officially making a lower
low. This is still a higher low here.
Still a higher low, holding support. If
we close the daily candle below, we have
made a lower low on the daily. And then
I have to change my tune. But market
structure is king. And right now, this
is bullish market structure. We're
flipping resistance into support and we
have bullish signs on the oscalator. And
so until we make a lower low, I have to
say, you know what? You know what? Let
me continue to huddle this juicy long
trade
from $58,500
because you know if we flip this thing
67k then I do think we can get vacuum
sucked up to the mid70s and and the
reason is simply because of this volume
profile. Remember having [music] now
hodddled this PC as support that means
the highest probability y'all is we come
up to value area high value area high
not only is value area high but if we
pull the fib from the high to the low
it's beautiful complence with that macro
golden pocket I mean you couldn't get
you couldn't get any more beautiful than
this I mean this is literally the most
beautiful thing I've ever seen when
people say picture the most beautiful
thing you could possibly imagine in your
I always think of this.
This is what I think of, guys. I think
of three different colored lines. Red,
orange, and green. Maybe red, yellow,
and green. Yeah, that's right. It looks
like a traffic light. It looks like a
traffic light. This is the traffic
light, guys. This traffic light. We're
going to have to look at the traffic
light as we come up here to see what
color is the traffic light. Is it green?
Can we blast through? Maybe the traffic
light's yellow. If the traffic light's
yellow, what does that mean? It means we
have to go as fast as we can. Boom. So
we can get through that traffic light
before it turns red. All right. Now, if
that traffic light's already red when we
get there, rejection.
Rejection. You know, we're going to send
this right back down. But until we get
to that traffic light, there really is
no resistance. All right. Now, hang on.
My treadmill has it slowed down.
I got to fix this treadmill.
Guys, I can't believe this treadmill
still works. I have to be honest. I'm
out here in the garage. The the sweat
that I have sweat while being out here
on this treadmill is so it's rivers
worth oceans worth. Okay, this table
that I'm using is the most disgusting
dried sweat thing. I have towels here
that I haven't washed in months and
they're disgusting. They smell horrible.
They're probably moldy. That's why the
towel's green. All right, speaking of
green towels.
Wow. Would you look at this green towel?
Wow.
Wow. Now this is a cool towel. Look at
how dirty this thing is, man. It's so
dang dirty. You could practically see
through it. All right. Big shout out to
Caleb Ford in the house. Shout out to J
Boy Bullish in the house. Shout out
Senor. He says, "Looks like a lot of
liquidity on the way down to Yeah,
that's another thing. Uh, yeah, Senor.
So, look, if we make a lower low on the
daily, then I'll tell you what I'm
expecting. It's pretty much the same
thing I was expecting last week. But
this is a flag. It this channel is going
to break up uh break out. It's going to
be broken
if we break down. Well, would you look
at this? You pull the fib from the low
to the high and we got another traffic
light here. Give or take. All right.
Give or [music] take. It's a confusing
traffic light here. All right. Cuz it's
it's yellow, red, green. All right. It's
it's a very strange looking traffic
light, [music] but nonetheless, we also
have the traffic light down here at
around $60,000. the ultimate traffic
light of confluence where honestly I
would say I would still be looking to
trade the range if we come down here
because shoulder head shoulder and if we
[music] you know just look at this here
like again like more times than not
especially in hindsight right in
hindsight you see something like this
this is the juiciest bullish divergence
in the world money flow curving to the
upside all right when you see that that
that it means if we do get a big drop
and if we actually get a momentum wave
coming down here. This momentum wave
here, especially as the money flow is
crossing up like this, is going to give
us a large juicy bounce. All right? And
here's here's how it works. It's going
to trick everybody into thinking we're
not going to get a juicy bounce
and then in hindsight, we're going to
get a bounce, right? We're be like,
"Dang, how did I not see that? It was a
beautiful bullish signal right down
here." You know, how did we not catch
that? You know, but yeah, honestly, like
this is my plan. if we come down lower.
Now, Jason, you say you're you're too
bullish. I've seen all the comments.
I've seen you guys out there in the
comments. I read the comments. I read
the comments on my smartphone when I'm
in the bathroom relieving myself. Going
number two. I read the comments. I see
what you guys say. Jason, you're so
bullish. How could you possibly be so
bullish, Jason? The bottom's not going
to be in until October. Until October.
You silly stupid crypto YouTuber. You
big shout out to my man James Shrill
2222 who says, "When you reach a one to
one, do you usually bring your stop loss
to break even?" Usually no.
Usually no. Usually no, honestly. Uh but
but but
as I was saying, people say, "Jay,
you're you're too bullish." All right.
You're too bullish. The bottom line till
October. Look, I can be bullish and
still expect another low, right? Who is
to say that we don't do something like
this and then do this and then our
bottoms in, right? Who is to say that?
In fact, I think that's probably kind of
plausible, right? Even if we do
something like this, we come down, we
get our shoulder, we come up, we hit the
golden pocket, then we come down. I
mean, guys, October, I mean, we have
some time. Like, what is it? July 27th.
All right. July 27th. October. That's
going to be coming in around here. We
got mad time. Look, I could draw this on
the chart. This thing I draw on the
chart. I mean, we literally have time,
right? We could still make another low.
We could range. We could chop. We don't
even have to come up through the golden
pocket. We could just break out of this
channel here, right? Hit our $70,000
level, right? We get the bounce. We come
up. We take the liquidity and we get a
failed auction and we get a big drop
down until October, right? It [music]
it's it just because I'm bullish now
doesn't mean I don't think we could come
lower cuz we absolutely can right but
the thing is so long as we're holding
above the PC right now we have to expect
higher locally as long as things are
looking this bottom down bullish here we
do [music] have to be open to higher
doesn't mean the bottom's in right might
be the the bottom might be in I don't
know
I know I'm a cheekologist you like but
Jay all you do is study the bottoms all
day you look is the left side bigger
than the right side. She's like, I know,
I understand. I go to the diner. Dolores
is my waitress. She comes out spilling
the coffee all over uneven glutius,
but look, I don't know if the bottom is
in. [snorts] All right. All I know is
that we have the significant uneven
glutius maximi right here. Dolores is
clearly at the diner right now. Clearly,
she's she's she's stumbling our coffee
over to the table right now as the price
is coming down to the keyboard. And you
could see right here the point of
control of the range. Like, do you see
this point of control of the range? See
where my cursor is? We're currently
right now we're back testing the PC of
the range. Right? It's a beautiful
picture right here. A beautiful picture
of a diner, waitresses with uneven
glutius maximi. People sitting down
smoking inside like it's the 80s. This
guy with a smart cigar. This guy with a
retail cigarette. All right. It's not
even real Marboro. It's like what's the
cheap brand? Pyramid or whatever they
sell. I don't know. I've never smoked
cigarettes in my life. But I do know
this guy can't afford no Marboro because
he doesn't know how to analyze the
bottoms. All right. Now, let's see where
we at. That's where we're at, man.
That's where we're at. Now, of course,
if we zoom in even more, right, let's go
to the 4our time frame. All right. Look
at what's happened here. From the high
to the low, we have smack dabbed into
the local Fibonacci golden pocket.
Right? Look at this. Look at this. Do
you see this?
So, we smack dab into the Fibonacci
golden pocket this morning after
bouncing from the PC. [music] So, we're
between a rock and a hard place right
now. Our local resistance, which must be
claimed for higher prices, [music] is
going to be the Casper pocket. All
right. between 65602 and 66152 and 90
cents on buy bit inverse perpetual USD.
All right, that's basically the Casper
pocket. And you know what else is cool
right now that we are bouncing from a
Fibonacci golden pocket as well. All
right, so these levels are mad
respected. All right, we're bouncing
from a Fibonacci golden pocket after
rejecting from a Fibonacci golden pocket
after bouncing from a PC after rejecting
from a PC. I mean, we are just playing a
game of ping pong here, right? Right. We
had the PC, we get rejection, right?
[music] PC rejection. We come down to
the PC. We get a bounceeronian cheese,
right? PC bounceronian cheese. We come
up to the Fibonacci golden pocket.
Straight up rejection. We come down to
the Fibonacci golden pocket. A good old
bounceronian cheese. All right. We're
smack dab in the middle. For me, this is
no trade zone right now. This is
literally a no trade zone. I am hoping
for some follow-through. I'm hoping to
finally break out of this channel either
to hit our tar at around 70,000 or hit
our tar to the downside at 60,000. Both
places in my opinion are where I'd be
looking for a new trade. If I was a
trader, if I was looking for a trade, if
I was in zero positions right now, what
would I be looking for? Where would the
next opportunities show themselves? For
me, it's very simple. [music] Okay, it's
very, very simple. For me, there's this
level here, this level up here around
the high that we made here on the
the 15th of June. Now, this is going to
be a zone because we have this high from
the 15th of June and we have this high
here from the 2nd of June. So, this
gives us a little bit of a box of
resistance where we need to be looking
for a fake out of the high of the range.
Right? First short trade opportunity is
[music] simply this. We come up and as
we're up here, people are very bullish.
Oh man, we're going to 73. But guess
what? We form a little bit of a range
and then we lose this level. Once we
lose this level, the Bart Simpson
pattern is likely to play out back down,
taking all of this, right? In that case,
I'm looking for a short trade. I'm
looking for bearish signals up in this
area. All right, to take it down to the
value area low of the range, right? This
is pretty much what I'm looking for. And
hey, maybe maybe the top is in and we
don't bottom out until October, in which
case, you know, hold the runner. pull
the runner. Right, the second short
trade I'm interested in is coming up to
the traffic light. Right, we got
ourselves a 73.3, which is a 74.1 zone
up here. And obviously, we need to be
looking for a rejection from the value
area high of the range all the way up
toward the 786. Which case, same deal.
We can be looking for a move back down
to value low. Or if that's it, honestly,
if we do reject from here, I would
expect we actually do come and make a
new low.
And then as far as the long trades go
right now, you know, I am if we get the
move down to the $60,000
uh support, I am looking for something
like this. I am looking for a bounce
from here. And I would be looking
eventually, why not to take it up to the
mid70s cuz that would be our final
target. Target number one would have to
be, you know, $70,000. Like if we do
come down to 60K right now before making
a high, target number one would have to
just be the high of the range here where
we look for short number one. And if we
don't see short number one, well, target
number two would have to be, you know,
at around $73,000,
right? Um, [music] but yeah, right now,
like, am I bullish? As long as we're
holding above this PC, yeah, I I would I
would like to see I I think we can see
more upside. I think that's still most
probable. And the only way for that to
change is a change of market structure.
Now, remember, changes of market
structure on the high time frame doesn't
necessarily mean short right away,
right? If we get a change of structure
on the daily time frame, what's that
tell us? That tells us we close the
candle here. Okay, it's officially now
we made a lower low, which means if we
back test now the PC, we can look for a
short entry, right? It doesn't mean to
short right away cuz if you short right
away, then where you you have to put
your stop loss above the last swing
high. And that's that's you know, or
maybe here that's too big of a stop
loss, right? Wouldn't we rather wait for
a back test? If we get a back test, then
we have a nice tight stop that we can
use, right? So, you know, the higher
time frames should be used to gather
your bias and help you figure out what
type of trade are you going to look for.
You know, if things are bearish, you're
like, well, I'm going to look for a
short if we get a back test of this key
resistance, right? Cuz right now, this
PC is major support. So, a short could
present itself here. If we lose it, we
back test it, then we make our way down
here. Take profit one on the short.
either look for the long trade or
[music] hold or take profit. I
personally I like to do both. I like to
TP1 on shorts. Even if I take a long,
I'm hold that short. That's just kind of
how I roll. You know, sometimes in life,
Jason, you just got to roll the dice.
You know, you just got to roll the dice
in life. Um,
you feel a freestyle coming.
You know what? I haven't felt a
freestyle coming myself.
There's there's one track that always
makes me freestyle no matter what.
It gets like real serious.
It's hard [music] to find.
It's this one. All of a sudden it gets
real serious.
This music gets real serious all of a
sudden.
You know, it makes me feel like I need
to FOMO into a trade. We have a super
chat.
Thank you, James, for the super chat. I
usually don't move my stop loss.
Antarctic will add for [music] 4x pairs.
Uh
man, this is so serious. Yeah. Uh
[music]
uh uh uh. [music] Hey yo, it's J C. You
know this so serious taking all the
trades but is your boy so delirious
outside I have to [music] pee and then I
take a piss inside the tree they call me
the white piss and now we're trading in
the house looking for the next golden
pocket for the golden bounce coming
[music] up to the red yellow green the
traffic light the bears and the bulls in
a fight cuz we're trading bitcoin all
day and all night until we get it right
[music] leverage got along the top
another liquidation baby loses stop. But
you know my trades only in the green.
[music] Cuz Jason Casper, he's a trading
machine. Now sit back. I'mma tell you
what I mean. I'll give it to you nice. I
never give it clean. Yeah. Never in
[music] the red. J Cash taking trades.
Got the bars up in his head. Yeah. It's
the best [music] crypto show. So sit
back and listen to the Jason Cash flow.
Here we go. I'm on my feet. We're from
the street. We're eating peas. You know
we like it. Baby, please [music] take
the cream cheese on your bagel. Spread
it on your knees. And that's what you do
when we squeeze [music]
all the shorts to the hot baby knees. H.
And then we got a big wick cuz the
Bitcoin price back to her old tricks.
The candles about to turn red. [music]
I got the bars in my head. But now the
candles are about to turn purple. Jason
Casper, he's such a nerd just like see
purple. But we don't want to see him
purple, only blue. Bitcoin will show you
what she going to do. Sit back and I'll
[music] take you to the trading scoop.
I'm so dang smart. Jason ain't no
stock. I'm about to show [singing] you
how to trade. [music] Yeah, cuz we're
here on the dread bill. My name is Bill
and you know we talking uphill. Got the
purple hat. Got to [music] flip it
around. J Casper trading Bitcoin all in
the town.
And then can you hear the sound? Bitcoin
[music] about to in the ground. Yeah. Uh
uh.
Yeah. That that that that that song
really does always get me get me feeling
something, too, you know.
[music] Oh my goodness.
Yeah, that that beat always makes me
feel something, guys. It always makes me
feel something.
Uh yeah, Antarctic definitely will add
the pairs in time. All right. In time,
Bitcoin will definitely add other pairs.
Right now, what do we got? We got gold,
we got silver. We got to refresh.
[music]
This thing been logged in since
Thursday. I haven't touched it.
Let's see what we got here. Yeah, right
now we got
we got gold and silver, [music] we got
QQQ, we got Spy, we got Nvidia, we got
Apple, we got Tesla, we got Amazon, we
got Google on this juicy decentralized
exchange. if you use my link, guys.
Super low fees. Super low fees. 0% limit
order. 0.02% market order. All right,
that is the deal with AX. But yeah,
eventually guys, we're going to be
adding we're going to be adding uh 4x
and all that kind of stuff on here. All
right, we're going to be able to do
everything on [music] this decks. All
right. On the decks. On the decks. On
the decks.
Um,
we could take Yeah, we'll take out we'll
check out SpaceX and we'll check out
gold.
Do we get into a low two leverage X with
our spot in Antarctic? Uh, they don't
have spot trading yet. All right, they
don't have spot trading yet.
Yeah, let's check gold. Let's check
Space X.
I hear voices. I hear voices, guys.
I hear voices.
Oh, okay. I hear voices. [music]
Let's check out real quick. We'll check
out gold.
Let's see. This is uh this was an idea I
had on gold here. Coming down to the
bottom here.
Let's check out gold real quick here.
So, gold is coming down to support. We
do have some bullish divergences here.
This was an idea I was playing with on I
did not take this trade, by the way. But
here's the thing about gold. We are very
bottomed out here on the weekly time
frame. [music]
We do have
uh I mean it depends on how you want to
if it depends on how you draw
divergences because some people go they
go wick to wick other people go body to
body. So if we're going body to body on
these weekly closes technically speaking
we do have some bull div here on the
weekly a double bottom on the weekly
this is a very rare signal. The last
time we had anything close to this guys
was back in
2022 and November. All right and that
was right here. Now, this was a very
beautiful looking
>> [music]
>> uh divergence in the sense that like
this whole range the lows were taken out
and then we we got a reclaim and we had
a triple bottom. All right, so it's not
quite the same, but we do have a very
very very bottomed out signal here.
[music]
And so, yeah, this is a potential idea
because
we have a bottomed out signal. And
basically, we're looking at this kind of
change of structure here [music] where
we have our low, we we take the low,
then we make a higher high, and we look
for the the retrace into this fib zone,
which we are bouncing from the 886, and
we have gotten [music] a move up from
there. So, there's real no sign of
strength yet on the weekly time frame,
right? I mean, on the weekly time frame,
there's real there's there's nothing
really [music] to say now is the time to
go in. But
that being said, I I think it is a valid
a valid entry. It's still a valid trade.
What would be a nicer trade? Honestly,
[music]
it would be to make one more low and
come down and take the liquidity at
38.88646,
right? Just take this low here. If we
take that low here and we get another
drive of bullish divergence on the
daily, I [music] mean that would just be
the most perfect signal, right? So, are
we being front run? Is the perfect
signal being front run? Maybe, you know,
maybe we do something like this and then
we come back in the range and form a
nicer looking accumulation pattern
before we squeeze all this cheese. You
know, we might squeeze all the cheese.
This would be my preferred setup on gold
here because that really would be ultra
bullish looking. you know, that would be
ultra bullish looking. And the last
time, let's see, in November 2023,
did we have something like this here?
Yeah. I mean, this is really what you'd
want to see, right? You would want to
see the low being going for again,
right? And then forming a nicer
accumulation range before the breakout.
So far, this this doesn't look super
convincing to me, right? This does not
look super convincing. Although yeah, we
do have bullish divs, it doesn't look
super convincing to me yet.
The only way it would start to look
super convincing to me is if we actually
did break out of this and hold above. In
which case, then I would say, you know
what, we did get front run that level.
Now, if we can get a back test of this,
then I that would be we could say, okay,
we have confirmed bulls divergence with
a break of market structure and now we
could look to squeeze all the cheese.
But you know, everyone has their own
risk tolerance. Risk apple tea. Tight
appetite. We got some tight apples up in
here. Let's take a look at SpaceX.
[music]
Oh my goodness. Wow. I didn't even I
have not even paying attention to SpaceX
at all. This is insane.
This is hilarious. Oh my goodness. Oh my
goodness. This is crazy. I actually did
not expect this.
I did not expect this. I mean, I
expected the initial selloff after the
listing, but I did not expect this. This
is [music] crazy, man.
Maybe it means SpaceX
sucks. I mean, maybe maybe they're not
really out there exploring space,
[music] right? I don't know what the
heck is going on here.
All right, so I'll be honest. There's
nothing I can say about this chart right
now. There's absolutely nothing I can
say about this chart. And here's why.
There there's no market structure.
[music] There's there's no data
historically to be looking at. There's
no Fibonacci to be looking at it. It's
just in straight freef fall slow grind.
What does that mean? Eventually this
thing is going to pump like crazy and
squeeze. All right. Like eventually it's
going to it's it's it's a it's a legit
company here. We're down 50%. So,
[music]
if I was interested in buying shares of
SpaceX,
not a bad time considering we're down
50% from when we listed, that's half
off. All right, that's half off. Um, so,
you know, you start to build the
position eventually. I do think we'll
probably come back to $170. I mean,
that's a 60% gain right there. I don't
know. Again, this is not financial
advice and I there's nothing I can look
at this chart to analyze, but when you
have something like this,
you know, a falling wedge pattern, I
mean, technically, you could even do do
it like this. And when you have
something like this for a legit company
like Space X, Elon Musk, the world's
richest man or whatever,
I mean, really, it's only a matter of
time before something happens with this
in my opinion, you know. But again, this
is not a technical trade. This is just
a, you know, when it's when something's
legit and it's beat down 50%, it's a
good buy objectively. It's half off, you
know. Sheesh. Is this real? I can't
believe this happened to SpaceX.
I cannot believe this happened to
[music] SpaceX.
That's crazy.
That is crazy. [music] You know, it's
not going to pump, says Virgin Devito. I
don't know. I feel like it will
eventually pump, man. Like that's how
stuff is. Like right now you're saying
don't it's not going to pump.
I don't know. I feel like that's when it
starts to pump. When people lose hope
and stuff, right? But hey,
don't listen to me.
It's not legit. You're only trading 4%
of the float. Really? It's only 4%.
All right.
Well,
this is pretty crazy. I cannot believe
this is SpaceX right now. That is pretty
crazy, man. That's crazy.
96% of the shares got unlocked. They're
going to pump. You know what? It would
not surprise me if this thing pumps,
man. I mean, it's Elon Musk. It's Elon
Musk. You know, I just have to defer to
it's Elon Musk. It's in a falling wedge.
It's 50% off. I don't know, man. I will
not be surprised. I will not be
surprised if we break and squeeze. I
would not be surprised at all when we
break and squeeze.
You know,
not at all. When we break and squeeze.
When we break and squeeze.
When we break [music] and squeeze.
You know when we break and squeeze.
When we break and squeeze.
Now, I'll be honest. Like, I'm not
buying [music] SpaceX. So, please don't
I am not Let me be honest. I am not
buying SpaceX. [music] I I don't
I don't even know. I I'll be honest with
you. Like, I don't even know if SpaceX
does anything real. I don't know. That's
That's where I'm at with it. I don't
even know if they [music] I mean, they
like launch a rocket off and then they
land it down in in the ocean and they
like have this giant celebration like
they just did something groundbreaking.
Like, what are they even doing? I don't
know. I don't know. Okay.
But
wouldn't surprise me if we pop, right?
All right. Yeah, SpaceX acting like an
altcoin.
Can you [music] barge that and pull it
over? I don't know what you're talking
about. Uh, Senor, was that for um was
that for uh gold?
We were looking at a You want me to
fractal it? I I [music] don't know now.
It's too late. It's past the point.
Um,
everyone in their grandma was going to
be a millionaire, but everyone's broke
now.
You know what's funny? Even if you are a
millionaire now, it doesn't even [music]
matter. Like a million dollars is like
nothing. Remember, who wants to be a
millionaire? You know, if you won that
show, it was like life-changing money.
Now, like if you win a million dollars,
that's like one-third of your
retirement.
You know, it's pretty crazy. A nickel A
nickel ain't worth a dime anymore, guys.
A nickel ain't worth a dime anymore.
I'll tell you.
How can you convince your brain and body
not to be glued to the chart and go to
the gym? I don't know, Cassra. Because
here's the thing. I I'm not a good
person to ask about that. I go to the
gym too much. I have a problem. All
right. I'm addicted to the gym. I work
out more than is beneficial. All right.
I [music] I So I I can't help you with
that. All right. I would say this. Once
you're working out, it's hard to stop.
Once [music] you have that sweet chest
pump going on the pecfly machine, it's
hard to stop, you know? So
everything is a meme coin until it
isn't.
Yeah.
Think about the babes at the gym.
Yeah, you know that that that doesn't
work for me at all. All right, there's
only one babe in my gym. That's my wife.
And if I think about her in the gym, I
usually don't get a good workout. All
right, so you can't be thinking about
babes when you're working out. All
right, you got to be thinking about you
got to be thinking about the mind muscle
connection. You know what I'm [music]
saying?
Trading Zen says, "Clickbait clown."
[music]
Welcome to the Jason Casper clickbait
clown show. Ladies and gentlemen,
hola miss amigosamo
s clickbait clown.
Welcome to my trading show. Can you
believe Jason Casper once again using
the clickbait thumbnails?
Let's even take a look at this one.
Let's see what it looks like. I forget
actually what it looks like.
Ah, look at that, man. That is that is
that is a that's a good thumbnail. Look,
got the FOMC. We got We got a P&L on
there. You know, [music] we got the
Ethereum logo, an arrow. Bitcoin's going
to break 65K. We did break 65K. This
ain't no clickbait. That's not
clickbait.
We did break 65K, but we rejected. But
yeah, we broke 65K, man. This ain't no
clickbait. This is the most real real
non-clickbait thumbnail I ever created
in my life. [music] All right.
Seriously, man. Um,
yeah. Click clickbait Carlos. Mayos
clickbait Carlos. Hola amigos. Meos.
Clickbait Carlos.
See, seenor
you working [music] out too much too.
Not not quicker. Yeah, me me too, man. I
don't know what it is. Like, look, I
just love working out. I love the
dopamine. I love the endorphins. I
[music] love lifting weights. And the
problem is when you lift weights too
much, you can't recover. And when you
can't recover, your strength goes down.
[music] And then you're just spinning
your dang wheels in the gym.
That's where I'm at right now. I got to
take like four days off. I got to take
like four days off right now. Got to
take like four [music] days off. You
know,
this morning I did I did an upper body
workout. I shouldn't have even done
that. I shouldn't have even done that. I
wasn't supposed to do it, but I woke up
and I felt kind of good. Here's the
thing. Sometimes you wake up and you
feel good. It's deceptive, right? I did
a heavy upper body workout, heavy lower
body workout, zero days off, then I did
another heavy upper body workout. It's
like, what the heck am I even doing
right now? Why am I doing that? you
know.
Um, [music]
yeah, I like my clickbait. I like my
clickbait lures as well,
you know. I like my I like my clickbait
thumbnails. [music] It's a tough time.
It's a tough time right now there to be
a crypto YouTuber, guys. I I'll, you
know, I'll be honest. I'll be totally
real. This is transparent Jay. All
right. This ain't no clickbait Carlos
talking. This is Transparent Jay.
Sometimes
I consider
just being done with YouTube. Going to
lie. Then I say, "No, no, I can't do it.
I can't I can't be done." All right.
There's too many reasons why I can't be
done. All right. I can't leave you guys.
I love you guys.
But uh yeah, it's been it's been a tough
time with YouTube. I'm not going to lie.
It's been pretty demotivating cuz the
whole crypto scene is totally dead right
now, you know. [music]
Yeah.
What?
Say it. Say it louder.
Yeah, man. Yeah. Yeah. I got you.
I got you.
It's been demotivating. I'm not going to
lie.
Um
at 60 back problems and arthritis.
[music]
Well, I you know, I reject that in Jesus
name, bro. Cuz you know what? I believe
the Lord can rejuvenate my joints.
But you know what? It also says, "Do not
put the Lord your God to a foolish
test."
So, look, I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm admitting
my sins and I'm I'm repenting. I'm
taking four days off. All right. I'm
going to come back.
trading only. Which do I make more money
in? Bull or bear? Well, I'll be honest
with you. This past bull and bare
markets, [music] I've made a lot of just
as much in both with just my trading.
Which is also one of the reasons why I
say, you know what, they should just
stop the whole YouTube. But nah, I'm not
going to stop YouTube, guys. I like it.
I do like YouTube. It just does become
unmotivating when, you know, you're
doing videos and stuff and it's just
like the channel is no friction. But it
is what it is, you know. It's it's it's
the crypto scene is changing. It's not
what it used to be. Like
I I've come to the I've come to terms
with the fact that we're never going to
have a 2021 hype again.
And we're probably never going to have a
2023 hype again because [music] the 2023
hype was everyone was expecting another
2020 2021,
right? You remember like March 2023?
March 2023,
right around here. I mean, in this area,
people were expecting another 2021,
2020, 2021. And then in the uh fall of
2023, this is where things really got
crazy. And people were, you know, all
right, this is it now. Like, you know,
we're going to we're going to blast off.
And then we just spent all this time in
the bull market doing nothing. And
everyone [music] lost all their hope in
crypto. Alts didn't pump. October 10th
wrecked everybody. And now [music] we're
going to enter into another silent bull
market here. And no one's really going
to give a crap really. We're probably
not going to come up much higher than
last [music] time. Maybe 150k,
you know, 180k at the at the most. And
even even if that happens, what are we,
you know, we're talking like, [music]
you know, 300%,
which that's not why people got into
cryp, you know, back in the day, people
got into crypto because we were doing,
you know, we were doing, you know, 2,000
3,000% on Bitcoin and plus way more for
these stupid altcoins. And it's just not
the same, man. You know, I miss those
days. I do miss those days. I'm not
going to lie. Like, I really do. I miss
those days. But it is what it is, you
know? And the funny thing is,
as a as a trader, I've come a long way
in all this time. Like, I'm way better
of a trader now than I was then. I make
way more money now trading than I did
then. But, uh,
the hype and all that and and the and
the dopamine and all that, you know,
that's that's that's gone. That's gone.
That's gone, you know.
That's gone.
more time in the Bible channel.
Yeah, I thought about doing that. You
know,
did I notice Bitcoin moves the same like
gold
and the Great Britain pound against the
US dollar? I mean everything kind of
everything kind of moves the same in the
sense that levels are respected, volume
is respected, divergences are respected,
support and resistance, everything
pretty much trades the same, but you
have to you have to get into the groove
of the asset you're trading. Like the
assets, even though the TA works the
same, [music]
you have to learn your asset, right? You
have to learn it. It's like any
relationship in life. You have to get to
know the other person, right? You know,
everyone's a human. Humans all kind of
work the same way, but you have to get
to know people individually, right?
That's the same with like Bitcoin. Like
Bitcoin and me, me and Bitcoin, I feel
like I have a special connection to
Bitcoin. I feel like I have a very
special connection to Bitcoin where I I
I could take trades on Bitcoin that I
could not take on any other asset.
[music] All right? I'm I'm willing to
take crazy trades on Bitcoin cuz I know
Bitcoin. I know Bitcoin. [music]
You know what I'm saying?
Now, I wouldn't be comfortable taking
those trades on Ethereum or on gold or
on Forex, you know, but yeah, in
general, everything's the same. It's all
about volume. It's all about support and
resistance, you know, Fibonacci [music]
volume.
I mean, that's that's pretty much I
mean, boil boil trading down. It's
literally support and resistance
and like some kind of edge, [music] some
kind of some kind of indicator. When I
say indicator, I don't mean an actual
indicator. Like I use an actual
indicator, but some kind of confirmation
to tell you to pull the trigger at
support or resistance. That's that's
really what it is, you know. Hang on, I
got to restart my dang
boom bap underground mix.
[music and singing]
Crypto is owned by governments now.
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean,
you know,
it is funny to look back and and realize
the
the big change in the crypto space cuz
I've been here since 2016. In 2016, it
was a whole bunch of anarchists, you
know, f the government, you know,
and and it it seemed like a almost like
an,
you know, it it was it was a big
movement in like the
the uh libertarian [singing]
kind of like anarchy [music]
subculture. And um
you know those people right now you know
I'm sure that they see what's happening
and they're disgusted by the fact that
Black Rockck has their hands on crypto
[music] and that you know governments
are now buying large portions of it and
even everything that's going on with
like micro strategy where [music] it's
becoming less and less decentralized and
everything that Bitcoin set out to be it
is not. you know, it meant to be a
peer-to-peer uh means of exchange,
[music] but it's turned into basically a
a thing that people have tried to uh use
to make money and now they celebrate
they celebrate the fact that, you know,
governments and large institutions, all
this are buying so much Bitcoin cuz in
the short term, yeah, it pumps our bags,
[music]
but I'm pretty neutral on like I don't
really care, you know, one way or the
other. I I'll be honest. I'm I'm
literally just here to make money. I I
don't care about the about the
technology. I don't think I don't think
Bitcoin is going to abolish all
governments and central banks. I don't
[music] think so.
You know,
shout out to Crypto Coons in the house
holding it down with the wrench.
How should you learn the asset? Should
you kiss Bitcoin? You can kiss Bitcoin.
You can do whatever you want to Bitcoin,
you know. You gota you gotta just do
smell smell the Bitcoin. Kiss Bitcoin.
Smell taste the Bitcoin. Listen to the
Bitcoin.
All five senses. All right. Touch,
taste, sight,
smell.
I don't know. I don't even know what the
five senses are, guys.
But all five you got to use. All right.
All five you got to use. [music]
One day Bitcoin [music] will be worth
infinity dollars. Yeah, maybe.
Look, I'm not going to lie, like I still
hold a bunch of Bitcoin. Like I I
haven't changed in that regard. When I
was younger, I I've put everything I had
into Bitcoin now that I'm old. I still
have a large portion of my net worth in
Bitcoin. something were to happen to
Bitcoin and I would lose a lot of money.
But I'm still bullish on it. I still
think we got a few years. I think I
would not be surprised to see Bitcoin at
500K.
Uh I wouldn't even be surprised to see
Bitcoin in a million. I would not be
surprised. It's It's only a 10x,
you know. It's not that crazy to think
that an asset could 10x. I've seen it do
way more than that in my lifetime,
you know. Um,
you know,
yeah. Taste the Bitcoin, all that stuff.
Bitcoin outperforms everything. Yeah,
Bitcoin has outperformed everything. Um,
which is still, you know, if if we're
going to be totally um
if we're going to be totally like
objective about it, that's not
necessarily a good thing.
Uh
because we've never seen any asset act
like Bitcoin ever. So, we've never seen
any asset act like Bitcoin ever. So, I
like to think that the trend will
continue and I do believe it will. And
I'm I'm if you were to look at my
actions, my actions prove that I'm I am
bullish on Bitcoin. My actions prove
that I believe that Bitcoin is going to
continue to go up based on how I buy
Bitcoin and hold Bitcoin and trade
Bitcoin and all this stuff, right?
But just because it's outperformed
everything in the last 20 years or so, I
mean really 16 years, right? We've gone
up 18
18 billion%
in the past [music] 16 years. I mean,
there's nothing we can compare this to.
We can't say what happened the last time
an asset went up 18 billion%.
You know, we don't know. We don't really
know. We've never seen anything come out
of nowhere
and and pump 18 billion%.
You know what I'm saying? So, like
Yeah. So we don't know like we don't
know
you know this and when you think about
this this this is not real life I mean
this is like living in a fantasy life I
mean honestly like
like
this is not normal right this is not
normal
and this is not sustainable let's be
honest this is really not sustainable
like th this obviously is not going to
the the the past is not going to be the
future we are not going to see Bitcoin
make proportionate gains in the future.
No way. Right.
So, but but I am bullish on Bitcoin. You
know, I am bullish.
Ramen noodles outperformed Ethereum.
[music]
You're going higher [music] percentage
into Micro Strategy over Bitcoin this
cycle and only trading a handful of
alts. Interesting, man. I'm I'm staying
away from Micro Strategy, you know. I am
staying away from micro strategy.
Bitcoin is the OG altcoin. Yeah, Bitcoin
is the OG coin, period. Right. Bitcoin
is the OG coin, period. Um,
come with me and we'll pee
in a big and beautiful
yellow bush.
Come with me to pee in the big beautiful
yellow bushes, guys.
Man,
I'm short from 655. A lot of liquidity
below 60. Yeah, crypto teeth. I I feel
you.
You know what? It's so funny. The green
screens on all my trees are are
completely see-through here, except for
the yellow bush that I'm peeing in.
That's funny.
You're losing hope. You bought Bitcoin
at 110K. Don't lose hope, man. If you
bought Bitcoin at 110K, let me just be
let me be frank with you. All right. Let
me be frank.
Um, you're you're good. Don't worry.
Don't worry. You you'll you'll be in
profit. I mean, yeah, you bought the top
and it it was a dumb move, but you know
what? Welcome to crypto. Welcome to
crypto. [music] And thankfully everybody
who who has ever bought the top is in
profit now. You know, man, look at look
at how weird this looks cuz of the green
screen, guys. Like the beautiful
countryside looks like gray and and and
and [music] disgusting out there, you
know? I'm not talking about the garbage
in my driveway. I'm talking about the
actual beautiful countryside out there.
It looks like gray and see-through. It
looks really weird. is so beautiful for
me, but for you guys it's ugly and
disgusting. It's depressing. Instantly
depressing looking at this stuff, you
know.
Doc [music] the goat, he says. He says,
"My male organs in hand and I'm talking
to hundreds."
No, I don't touch it. Look, I do the
hands 3P, baby. You know, I do the hands
three P and the way I shake it off is I
just wiggle the hips like Elvis,
you know. Just wiggle the hips like
Elvis,
you know. Don't worry, I'm not that
gross.
[music] Shout out to memory, man. What's
going on, my bro?
[music] God is watching you pee in the
bushes. Yeah, God watches everything
that we do. Everything that we do.
[music] And someday our entire life is
going to be reviewed. Isn't that crazy?
Isn't that crazy? Everything. Everything
we do, God knows. And God's everywhere.
It's weird to think about, but it's
true. What do I use to mow my yard? A K
Cabota tractor with a 60-in mower deck.
That's what I use. [music] You know,
how's New York Booze?
I haven't been to New York in a long
time. I haven't been to New York since
September.
And I haven't had [music] booze in New
York for a long time. Last time I drank
in New York was
probably [music] in 2012.
Yeah.
Didn't [music] wash my hands. Yeah, I
didn't wash my hands. But here's the
thing, guys. I do wash my hands. I know
people say I don't. Guys, just a quick
reminder. All right.
[music]
Blowoffin is giving away $2,000 every
week. All right,
$2,000 a week.
Blowin is giving away. And the way you
are available to enter this is [music]
you go into my Discord, my free Discord
or my paid Discord here. Let's uh let me
show you guys exactly how to win.
[music] It's actually a legit uh awesome
thing they're doing. Bit basically $500
a week. All you have to do for that is
sign up.
What the heck did I just do?
Hang on. [music]
Yeah, Bitbase is giving away $500 a
week, but right now Blowfin is giving
away $2,000 a week. In order to enter,
all you have to do is post a screenshot
of your Jason Cash for Blowfin PNL. So,
if you sign up using my link, your P&Ls
will look like this. I know, I know.
Makes me very uncomfortable, too. All
right. So after you get these P&Ls, you
post them in this channel and every time
you post a P&L, [music] you're entered
into the raffle. You can get as many as
you want. So you can enter into the
raffle many, many times.
Uh
VIPs get three entries per submission.
NonVIPs get one entry per submission.
And every week, four winners are going
to get $500 [music] right into their
blowfin account. So, sign up, use my
link, join the free Discord or the paid
Discord for your chance to win. Also,
guys, quick reminder that Bitbase
[music] is giving away $500 a week.
Plus, they're giving you VIP level seven
fees and all these juicy signup bonuses.
All right. So, also if you want to join
the Casper crew, jason caspertrading.com
to get into the VIP Discord.
Uh,
when you buy Bitcoin at the top, you
didn't lose anything but a little time.
Yeah, if you buy Bitcoin at the top,
like honestly, just hold out because
again, you you look at the chart and
[music] everyone's made out well.
$110,000 is is not the top for Bitcoin.
Okay. So, yeah, it sucks right now
because you're down quite a bit. You are
[music] down, let's see how much you're
down.
You're down about 42%. And I wouldn't be
surprised if you end up down about 64%.
But then next cycle,
let's say my conserved target of 150,
you'll be up 30%. You know, that's not
so bad. And if we hit my more liberal
target between 180 and 200
potentially, [music]
you know, you're going to be up 50%.
[music] You know, 50 to 70%. So, I think
it's still a good thing. And if you're
holding out for the long term,
you know, then I do think that uh
yeah, it's only 64%. Hector Rodriguez,
[music] look, where I went to high
school, that's still a passing grade.
All right. You could still pass up until
59% was a was a fail. All right. So, you
could still pass. You could still pass.
You know,
you could still pass the dang class.
You could pass the dang class,
man.
[music]
Oh man. Shout out to 20 [music] 2020
2025 resurrection with the bars.
Yeah. Uh uh. Yeah. [music]
Uh yeah.
I could feel these bars. Yeah. Don't
[music] you know, baby? Pissing like a
champ. Pure relief from [singing]
within. Golden showers for the foliage.
So, um I I [music] lost my flow. I lost
my flow with your bars,
but
I like the bars. I do like the bars.
Uh, on the other hand, your 401k might
not do so good, says memory man.
Shout out to 80s302.
What's the second green line in the
short box?
Those are just the two highs of the
local range. Just the two highs of the
local range here. So, if we go down to
like our 4hour time frame, we have like
these highs over here.
This like little 4hour dogee.
Just a little bit of liquidity.
Little bit of liquidity.
When the market's boring, it's time to
get ready with the storm. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. The storm's coming, guys.
Are we going to zero? Nah, we're good.
Don't worry, guys. Don't worry. Look,
Bitcoin's good. Bitcoin's not going
Bitcoin's not going anywhere anytime
soon. We still got some good years
ahead. I have a very strange bump on my
arm. I don't know what it is. I don't
know what it is. ingrown hair maybe.
I don't know. Ingrown hair.
Maybe a pimple. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know what that is.
Did I end up selling the Bugatti I got
from Carl?
I sold the Bugatti, but I didn't sell
the Big Mac. The Big Mac is still on my
desk. Hasn't gone rotten.
Is bluffing only for new accounts? No,
it's for anybody who has a who who has
the P&Ls with my P&Ls. All right.
Um, shout out to Johnny HSV. God bless
you, man.
All right. All right. Well,
with all the lost Bitcoin mods, it's
impossible for Bitcoin to go to zero in
my opinion, says Cryptocoons. Yeah, I
don't think Bitcoin is going to go to
zero. [music]
But yeah. All right, guys. I think I'm
going to head out cuz I don't really
have anything else to say. So, God bless
you guys.
Have a great day. Have a great night.
I'll see you later. Peace.